http://www.finerribbon.com/privacy-statement.html

Privacy statement
Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy!
FinerRibbon.com will oc casionally update its privacy statement to reflect company and customer feedback. When FinerRibbon.com posts changes to this privacy statement, the date of the update will be displayed at the end of this statement. If you have questions or concerns about policy changes, you should first contact the FinerRibbon.com customer service department by Clicking Here or by calling 514-570-5196.
How We Use Gathered Information
FinerRibbon.com may request personal information, including your name, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, billing address, credit card number, and expiration date. FinerRibbon.com collects the requested information in order to:
Process an order.
Verify your identity for payment authorization.
Contact you regarding your order status.
Ship your order to you.
Maintain an order history for future support.
Enter you in a contest or sweepstakes (only if you wish to participate).
Send you news from FinerRibbon.com (if you sign up to our newsletter).
Provide you with the best online shopping experience.
Once FinerRibbon.com gathers your name and address, this information will then be transferred to your credit card company, if applicable, for confirmation to complete your purchase. Your shipping information may also be supplied to a third-party fulfillment center, but your information will not be used for any other purpose than delivery of your order. Your name and address will not be sold to mailing-list firms or any mass advertising entities.
Third Party Privacy Policies
FinerRibbon.com gives you access to third party partners to provide you with certain services that are detailed below. FinerRibbon.com will provide that third party with your transaction information and then that third party will collect additional information that it needs to provide you with the requested service. FinerRibbon.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from FinerRibbon.com so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use, and share your information. FinerRibbon.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or content on Web sites outside of the FinerRibbon.com Web site.
Participation in Contests or Sweepstakes
If you choose to participate in a FinerRibbon.com promotion (contest or sweepstakes), FinerRibbon.com may share your personal information with those organizations running the applicable promotion. Personal information is usually shared in order to ensure your ability to redeem that promotion with the third-party partner managing that promotion. FinerRibbon.com verifies that these third parties do not use your information for any other purpose other than to manage the promotion.
Tracking of Advertising Links, Action Tags, and Cookies
FinerRibbon.com works with a third-party advertising company to collect information on advertisement performance and Web site usage. This company serves FinerRibbon.com ad banners on our behalf which use action tags and cookies to measure how many times users view and click on an ad and which specific pages of our Web site users visit (e.g. a product page or our homepage). To do so, this company may use information about your visits to the FinerRibbon.com Web site and other Web sites. Unless otherwise notified, our third-party advertising company does not use names, addresses, e-mail addresses, or telephone numbers and does not link any online actions or cookies to an identifiable person. The use of your cookies is subject to this privacy policy.
FinerRibbon.com Communication
FinerRibbon.com offers customers many ways to keep up to date with the latest product offerings and promotions as well as contacting our staff for sales inquiries or support. The following points outline how we use your information.
"Send To Friend" Feature
When you e-mail a product to a friend, you and your friend's names and e-mail addresses are requested. This ensures that your friend will know that you have requested that FinerRibbon.com send them an e-mail. You and your friend's e-mail addresses will only be used for this purpose.
Refer a Friend
Using our online form, you can also refer a friend to the FinerRibbon.com Web site. You and your friend's names and e-mail addresses are requested to ensure that your friend will know that you have requested that FinerRibbon.com send them an e-mail. You and your friend's e-mail addresses will only be used for this purpose.
Surveys
FinerRibbon.com occasionally requests information from our users and customers via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary, and all participants have a choice whether or not to disclose information. The requested information typically includes the customer's first name, as well as information relating to the customer's experience at FinerRibbon.com, or their opinions on products they have purchased. Survey information will be used internally to monitor or improve our site, and after attaining user permission, may be posted on the site to provide information about our products to other users. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties.
Opt-Out Policy
To opt out of receiving communications from FinerRibbon.com, just select "unsubscribe" from your account page and you will opt out of receiving any further communication immediately. You may also contact us directly at 514-570-5196 or by e-mail by Clicking Here, and one of our consultants will provide immediate assistance.
Updating Your Account
If the personal information FinerRibbon.com has gathered from you changes or you no longer desire our service, we will gladly correct, update, or remove any personal data you have previously provided to us. To request a change or removal of your personal information, send an e-mail by Clicking Here or contact us at 514-570-5196. You may also update or delete your personal account with us from your account page.
Security
FinerRibbon.com is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. To protect the information you send from your computer to FinerRibbon.com's e-commerce system, this information including your credit card number, name, and address is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. We use encryption and Web security technologies to protect the privacy of your personal data on our own internal servers and the security of our servers are monitored daily and verified by a dynamic logo displayed on our site pages. Only parties responsible for processing your order have access to your credit card and bank information. FinerRibbon.com continuously reviews its policies and practices to ensure that all customer information remains secure.
Use Of Browser Technology
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer hard drive. You must have cookies enabled in order for you to be able to perform many of the general functions on the FinerRibbon.com Web site. With cookies enabled, the FinerRibbon.com Web site will have the capacity to deliver you a more customized and complete shopping experience to track visits from our affiliates and partners and to enable the use of our shopping cart. FinerRibbon.com does not use cookies to store or collect any personal information such as names, addresses, or payment information. To learn how to enable cookies on your computer, visit the Web site that corresponds to the browser you use:
Microsoft Internet Explorer
Netscape
Mozilla / Firefox
IP Addresses
FinerRibbon.com collects your IP address, which cannot be used to identify you personally, to help diagnose problems with its server, to administer and tune the operation of its site, and to log your browser type and referring URL information. FinerRibbon.com's servers use each IP address to anonymously track the date and duration of each session within its site. Your IP address may also be used to help FinerRibbon.com collect statistical data or in gathering broad usage information. Your IP address may also be used to verify the validity of your order in order to ensure that no fraudulent orders are processed.
Contacting FinerRibbon.com
Via the "Contact Us" link, FinerRibbon.com allows customers to contact our staff. This provides direct contact to a FinerRibbon.com fine jewelry consultant, who reads each e-mail and tries to promptly answer your questions. FinerRibbon.com may also file your comments to improve the site and program or review and discard the information. You may also send us your comments about the FinerRibbon.com Web site or the shopping experience in general, as we always appreciate feedback. It is our strict policy to reply to all inquiries.
Protection Against Fraudulent Charges
If a third party obtains your personal information from a purchase made with FinerRibbon.com and uses that information to perpetrate credit card fraud, you are legally protected. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank may hold you liable for up to $ 50.00 USD of fraudulent charges. If your bank holds you liable for any portion of the $ 50.00 USD, FinerRibbon.com will cover up to the entire $ 50.00 USD. FinerRibbon.com will cover this liability if the unauthorized use resulted through no fault of yours from purchases made on FinerRibbon.com's secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card company in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.
Legal Disclaimer
The only time Multicolor Enr. will disclose personal information is when required to by law or with the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the law. If you have questions about this privacy statement, please contact the FinerRibbon.com customer service department by Clicking Here or by dialling 514-570-5196.
FinerRibbon.com is a wholly owned subsidiary of Multicolor, a federally and provincially registered Canadian company.
Question?
